A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Senior Advisor, Office Files of Frank DeGiovanni FA1876
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Senior Advisor, Office Files of Frank DeGiovanni
1990-2016
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
DeGiovanni, Frank
FA1876
27.48 Cubic Feet 69 document boxes: 55 letter boxes and 14 legal boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at the RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files, and officers' papers were transferred to and accessioned by the RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
This material was transferred to the RAC in eight accessions between 2020 and 2024 and was ingested by the RAC as Accessions 2020:013, 2020:036, 2021:141, 2022:031, 2022:057, 2023:024, 2023:075, and 2024:072.
Arrangement
Collection is comprised of two series.
Original order was maintained as much as possible.
The collection arrangement is as follows:
Series 1. Frank DeGiovanni notebooks, 1995-2013
Series 2. Subject files, 1990-2016
Scope and Contents
The collection contains the office files Frank DeGiovanni created and maintained when he worked at the Ford Foundation for over 20 years. The files primarily originate from DeGiovanni's positions as Director of the Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit, Director of the Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit, and Senior Advisor to the President. There is a smaller amount of material from DeGiovanni's time as a Program Officer and then Deputy Director of Program Related Investments (PRI).
The collection consists of two series. The first series contains notebooks Frank DeGiovanni created and used throughout various points in his career at the Foundation. DeGiovanni's subject files are contained in the second series and comprise the bulk of the collection.
Subject files regarding DeGiovanni's leadership of the Ford Foundation's programming for asset building and economic development provide insight into almost 20 years of activities and strategy for the Foundation's engagement in those fields. Grants, projects, and initiatives focused on:
- Financial asset building and economic security for lower income families, poverty reduction, access to financial services, savings accounts
- Development finance, equitable economic development, and pro-poor development
- Community development
- Microfinance
- Sustainable development, rural development, value chains, and food security
- Consumer protection and consumer credit
- Housing, homeownership, and mortgages
- Economic policy
- Program Related Investments (PRI) and impact investing
Subject files created during DeGiovanni's role as Senior Advisor to the President document the Ford Foundation's strategy development for its Thematic Areas and Regional Offices between 2015 and 2016.
Common material formats found throughout the collection include correspondence, memos, notes, drafts, reports, proposals, articles, meeting materials, and presentation materials. There are also a few photographs and some digital media.
Ford Foundation; Community development; Consumer credit -- United States; Consumer protection; Economic development; Economic policy; Economic security; Financial security; Financial services industry; Food supply; Housing; Investments; Microfinance; Mortgage loans; Poverty; Rural development; Savings accounts; Sustainable development
- Frank DeGiovanni notebooks, 1995-2013; 1; .57 Cubic Feet 1.5 document boxes: 1.5 letter boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains notebooks Frank DeGiovanni created and used throughout most of his career at the Ford Foundation. There are a set of notebooks that were dated and a set of notebooks that were numbered. The dated set was arranged chronologically during processing, and the numbered set was ordered numerically and placed after the dated notebooks in the series.
  DeGiovanni used the notebooks for meetings, "to dos", program strategy, and other activities.
  Other documents were inserted into the notebooks like other notes, correspondence, meeting materials, and business cards.
  - July 1995-July 1996 notebook, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - October 1996-November 1997 notebook, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - November 1997-January 1998 notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - January 1998-April 1998 notebook (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - April 1998-July 1998 notebook (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - July 1998-May 1999 notebook, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - June 2006-September 2007 notebook, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - November 2007-June 2008 notebook, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - March 2008 notebook (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - June 2008 notebook (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - June 2008-January 2009 notebook, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - January 2009-August 2009 notebook (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - June 2009 notebook (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - October 2011-June 2012 notebook, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - June 2012-April 2013 notebook, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - July-August notebook, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Frank DeGiovanni notebook 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Frank DeGiovanni notebook 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Frank DeGiovanni notebook 3, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Frank DeGiovanni notebook 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Subject files, 1990-2016; 2; 26.91 Cubic Feet 67.5 document boxes: 53.5 letter boxes and 14 legal boxes
  This series contains the subject files Frank DeGiovanni created and maintained throughout his various positions at the Ford Foundation. There are two main groups of files that are intermixed throughout the series. One group documents DeGiovanni's leadership of the Foundation's asset building and economic development programming, and the other documents his work as Senior Advisor to the Foundation's President. There are also a few records that originate from the time DeGiovanni worked in the Foundation's Program Related Investments (PRI) as a Program Officer and then Deputy Director.
  DeGiovanni created the files pertaining to the Foundation's asset building and economic development programming when he served as Director of the Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit and then Director of the Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit. These records document the Foundation's engagement with financial asset building and poverty reduction for lower income families, increasing access to financial services, promoting savings and children's savings accounts, development finance, pro-poor development, microfinance, sustainable development, value chains, food security, consumer protection, housing, and impact investment.
  Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI), Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL), Improving Access to Financial Services, and Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) were major initiatives of the programs DeGiovanni led. Many files document the Foundation's partnerships with organizations like the Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP), Self-Help Ventures Fund, and the University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC).
  The files also show DeGiovanni's broader activities as a director of these units. There are materials regarding meetings, trips, administration, program strategy, and budget. His management of Program Officers is documented within Program Officer Memos and specific meeting files.
  The files DeGiovanni created as Senior Advisor to the President regard the Ford Foundation's larger strategy development through its Thematic Areas and Regional Offices between 2015 and 2016.
  - Assessing the Impact of Microenterprise Services (AIMS) papers, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Impact assessment of microenterprise, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Impact assessment, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Finance Development Impact Assessment Project, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Finance Development Impact Assessment Project, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Finance Development Impact Assessment Project - Presentations on impact assessment, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Community Development Financial Institutions (CDFI) impact assessment, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Finance and Development Research Programme Papers, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit - Program Related Investments (PRI), part 1, 2007-2013 (Box 3, Folder 29-32)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit - Program Related Investments (PRI), part 2, 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - March 2014 India trip (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Initiative for Smallholder Finance (ISF) Steering Committee Meeting, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Skoll Foundation April 2014 World Forum (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Self-Help Ventures Fund/University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital, 1998-2014 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) funding proposal, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - February 2014 Mexico trip (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Better Than Cash Alliance (BTCA), 2014 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL), 2013 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) Monitoring Survey, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Community Science - Financial Products and Services report, 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - July 10, 2012 meeting with Luis Ubinas (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) Universal Standards for Social Performance Management (SPM), 2012 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF), 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Microsavings and Payments Innovations Initiative (MPII) research, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Living Cities Capital Formation, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Imp-Act Consortium Business Plan, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Grameen Foundation Social Performance Management Center, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Homeownership communications work, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit - Miscellaneous meetings, 2006-2012 (Box 5, Folder 53-54)
  - Marketplace Wealth and Poverty, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - November 20, 2011 biweekly meeting with Pablo Farias, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Theory of Change revised, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) November 2011 meeting, Nairobi, Kenya (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - January 2012 Weekly Leadership Meeting (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) September 2011 Retreat (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2013 grants, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit meeting reports, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Pipeline, circa 2013 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Fiscal Year 2012 program assistant appraisal process (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Results Reporting Guidance, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL), undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Presentation to Luis Ubinas - Financial Assets unit initiatives, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Messaging for asset building programs - Survey research, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Frank DeGiovanni memos to Pablo Farias - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities to Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI), 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2013 budget, 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - United States Financial Diaries Project - Fieldwork Extension Proposal (FEP), 2013 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Foundation Administered Projects (FAP) - Budget, 2009-2012 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Financial Assets unit Economic Opportunities for Rural Poor, Mexico and Central America - Program Officer job description, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2012 grantmaking, 2009-2011 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Program Relation Investments (PRI) presentation - Ford Foundation Trustees, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Kilolo Kijakazi monthly meetings and work, 2010-2012 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Ford Foundation Program Related Investments (PRI) Innovation Check-in - Monitor Deloitte, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Mountain Association for Community Economic Development (MACED), 2013 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Central Appalachia Network (CAN), 2013 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) United States evaluation request for proposal, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - United States Financial Diaries Advisory Board, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Economic Policy Research Institute (EPRI) 2011 grant - Evaluation of savings and investment linkages of South Africa's child support grant (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) 2011 internal audit memos, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program 2015 Group, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Seal of Excellence for Poverty Outreach and Transformation in Microfinance, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Root Capital grant proposal - Food security and nutrition, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Sustainable Food Lab (SFL) and Catholic Relief Services (CRS) concept paper - Agricultural value chains, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees February 2012 Meeting - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) review (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Amy Brown - Fiscal Year 2012 grantmaking, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Wayne Fawbush - Fiscal Year 2011-2012 grantmaking, 2010-2012 (Box 7, Folder 90-91)
  - Financial Assets unit Program Officer for Enhancing Rural Livelihood Opportunities for Rural Poor, Jakarta, Indonesia Office - Interview notes, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Financial Assets unit Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Program Officer, New Delhi, India Office - Position search, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Expanding Livelihood Opportunities for Poor Households Initiative (ELOPHI) Initiative Summary Input Program Officer Forms, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Retreat - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit description, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Better Than Cash Alliance (BTCA) launch, 2004-2012 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Better Than Cash Alliance (BTCA) launch - Frank DeGiovanni MC materials, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) restructuring, 2006-2011 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) 2007 redesign (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Fiscal Year 2011 Loss Reserve Adjustments (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) Global Travel Learning Fund, 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit travel and meeting budget Fiscal Year 2012 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) projections Fiscal Year 2013 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) projections Fiscal Year 2012, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Mid-Year Loss Reserve Review April 2012 Meeting (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) 2013 revised projections (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Fiscal Year 2014 Pipeline, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2013 travel and meeting budget (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Program Related Investments (PRI) Year End Loss Reserve September 2011 Meeting, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Poverty targeting, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) Meeting - Improving the Impact of Microfinance on Poverty: Action Research Programme (IMP-ACT), 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - South Africa programming, 2009-2010 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Savings-Linked Conditional Cash Transfer Colloquium, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - ShoreBank, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit miscellaneous materials, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - National Consumer Law Center (NCLC), 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Living Cities The Integration Initiative (TII) March 2010 Meeting, Washington D.C. (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - ShoreBank, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) 2010 General Meeting, Bern, Switzerland (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Savings-Linked Conditional Crash Transfer Colloquium, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Americans For Financial Reform (AFR), 2010 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Miscellaneous materials - Conference preparation, grant proposals, budget, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Quicksilver - Ford Foundation Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Brand Framework, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Living Cities - Theory of Change discussion, undated (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) August 2010 Global Meeting (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit initiatives - Scope of work for consultant to assist learning and evaluation, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - August 2010 notes (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Strategic Communications Workshops, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Miscellaneous materials - Initiatives and grantees, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 129-130)
  - Overcoming Inequality and Structural Poverty in South Africa Conference, 2006-2010; File contains digital media (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Overcoming Inequality and Structural Poverty in South Africa, undated (Box 10, Folder 131)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Miscellaneous materials - Strategic planning, initiatives, grantees, 2004-2010 (Box 10, Folder 132-133)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Line of Work Statements, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Mortgage Reframing Project, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program meeting, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Innovations for Poverty Action (IPA) Targeting the Ultra Poor (TUP) evaluations, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Qualitative Research - Graduation Program, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Living Cities Capital Formation Working Group, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Meetings with Representatives, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Line of Work Statements conference calls, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Economic Opportunities and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit web page overview, 2007-2009 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Ford Foundation Worldwide Meeting Plenary on Development, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Community Capital (CCC) - SaveNYC evaluation, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) Impact Measurement assessment, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) d/b/a The Financial Innovations Center.
    The Center for Financial Services Innovation (CFSI) is now called the Financial Health Network.
  - BRAC poverty scorecard, undated (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - June 2009 Communications Workshop (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Harvard University Joint Center for Housing Studies - Various conferences, 2003-2010 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Ford Foundation Meeting with University of Chicago Faculty, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Financial Assets and Economic Security Fiscal Year 2009 budget overview (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Financial Assets and Economic Security Fiscal Year 2009 budget review meeting (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Critical Research and Policy Priorities for United States Department of Housing and Urban Development, April 2009, Washington D.C. (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Program Officer recruiting, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)/World Bank - Building Inclusive Financial Systems: Donor Guidelines on Good Practice in Microfinance, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Omidyar notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - International Development Research Centre (IDRC), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Thembaur notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - SEEP Network October 2005 meeting, Washington D.C., 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - ShoreBank, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Ford Foundation November 2008 Worldwide Meeting, New York City, New York (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Line of Work Statements, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Social Performance Taskforce (SPTF) - Meetings, correspondence, and projects, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Aspen Institute Initiative on Financial Security (IFS), 2006 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Ford Foundation Corporate Involvement Initiative (CII) strategic assessment, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program (EOA) Financial Assets unit Fiscal Year 2010 - Administration, programming, and budget, 2004-2010 (Box 11, Folder 165-166)
  - Center for Financial Inclusion at Accion International (CFI) - Campaign for Client Protection in Microfinance, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Living Cities Catalyst Fund, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Center for Financial Inclusion at Accion International (CFI) - The Smart Campaign, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Savings-Linked Conditional Cash Transfer Colloquium, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Scaling Up, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) executive officer search, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    Restricted – Executive Search – Open in 2051
  - Kilolo Kijakazi - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED), 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - KWFT request to renew Program Related Investments (PRI) loans, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Social Indicators Project, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - Caroline Moser, Brookings Institution - Assets, Livelihoods, and Social Policy, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - Ecotrust, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - Microfinance institutions, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - Ford Foundation Meeting - First Nations Development Institute's Oklahoma Asset-Building Policy and Practice, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) Executive Committee (EXCOM), 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - Innovations for Poverty Action (IPA) - Ghana Microfinance Graduation Pilot proposal, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - Tony Sheldon - Social Performance Task Force (SPTF) Annual General Meeting, June-July 2010, Bern, Switzerland (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - June 2010 Quarterly Meeting with Luis Ubinas (Box 12, Folder 183)